So welcome to your channel Stock
Market friends I hope you guys are good
so friends here you
can see the numbers and quarters of ICICI Lombard properly 90
and ICICI Lombard is a general insurance
company this company has liked
definitely
subscribe and if
we do it here then the
result that I have given you here is a
little bit no
problem I will tell you something strange but in that
I am
generating you the complete proper total last year the company made
23 thousand rupees 3 lakh
5851 rupees more 91 so right now the company did a good
amount of Vijay employment here last year
but is the same thing happening this year as well
or not see let me
talk about that your what the company is doing this year is 3
lakh 85 thousand
414 means that the company is seen showing a jump here straight away
good jump from the
quarter so if we talk about the
quarter it is good for the jump the
experts of the company the business of the company is around three lakh
80 thousand eight hundred sixteen lakh rupees  Quite
early clearly the company is
seen to be improving a lot, by
clicking on this I it will look proper to you, so
here you can see that currently the
company has
414 area, it is doing business here, but
how much the company is spending in the year of doing business matters a lot, so the
expense total expense, I have put it here,
how much a special company is
spending for doing its business,
so here you will see on the upper
line that last year the company was spending 2 lakh 74 thousand
600 82 lakhs, Jogni 588 17
lakhs in the last quarter, the company's
expenses have also increased, let's
see how much it is earning after spending,
here first the company
1353 likes
subscribe means if we talk about the company then it is
not getting much at all, in the last year there
was a decline of 44668 lakhs, this company is definitely incurring loss while doing
business, but the
company is seen to be incurring loss as I am telling you  Let me tell you
that the situation of the company was bad and the life
insurance situation was bad, the
shareholders i.e. their policy holders have to pay the tiffin, the
company
goes to the office tomorrow and asks when does the criminal PM
come, but if you have to pay a lot, you have to pay a lot, if
you take a term insurance of ₹400 then ask
how much is the total premium, one means you will have to pay
one crore,
but the company is paying 413 crores, these things happen that it was
not taken from 401 people, that is at
least as much as the company's policy is from them,
but this time the company has to pay a
lot and to
earn their income, that is why companies are seen investing,
so friends, if we talk about today
in ICICI Lombard, you can see
that the stock had fallen earlier, there was a
decline in the stocks since morning
and that happened directly, in this there is a little
participation in the market fall, so
if the part of the stock taking so much would
definitely have been arrested, but it was not so much, if we
talk about one month, the pass in the stock
today  The organization is giving a red chilli
stark Nick Guru returns of five questions
means that the stock has been
seen in the same momentum for a long time Shyam you will get to
see many companies in it
Maximum chart pattern company used to
break 1720, since then it has been limited to 108, which means very
high returns are being given, hey if you
get different, then the company is giving additional returns, it is
not that it does not depend, the
company has given good returns in the 15 years since 2017, if we talk about the
long-term perspective of the company, the
numbers are correct right now because America, Britain
is good, a little profit of the German company has been
cut in the quarter, there can be a little decline
also and how much will the decline be
friends, you can see for 1 year, I will put
and here you will see
that the company has already made strong support many times
and after that you will
also see the company getting arrested,
meaning that the company can hold 1340, three hundred and fifty, if there is a
decline then there can be a fall of ₹50 more,
that will show the reversal again today, so in
this from long-term perspective,
now continue  You can do a hundred tomatoes, they
need a little fighting, friends I hope you liked the
video, then please like it and
share it as well, you will keep getting information,
today the numbers of many companies like Anti
are out and many other companies like Master
etc., Bajaj Auto, after that directly the
numbers of these, you will know everything, how are they going to be, so
just subscribe to the channel and
keep it along with the bell icon, so
that you will keep getting the latest updates of the new
video, friends, tomorrow also you can go and
watch the update of many numbers along with a ward, see you
friends
in the next video, till then bye-bye take care